<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Jeremy Avens]]></title><description><![CDATA[NBN Holdings]]></description><link>https://www.nbn.qa/blog</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 19:56:15 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.nbn.qa/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[The Launch of The New Corporate Branding]]></title><description><![CDATA[A new branding that will launch Nasser Bin Nawaf &#38; Partners Holdings to new heights both nationally and internationally. Nasser Bin Nawaf...]]></description><link>https://www.nbn.qa/post/new_brand_identity</link><guid isPermaLink="false">61c9b0d371edb60016139607</guid><category><![CDATA[Corporate]]></category><pubDate>Mon, 27 Dec 2021 12:25:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/eb9f3f_1e5848719d5b41989a5b1e27e7ecb254~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Gregory de Maiche</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>A new branding that will launch Nasser Bin Nawaf & Partners Holdings to new heights both nationally and internationally.</strong></p><figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/eb9f3f_7e506bc669a044eab15b5e428b8898d6~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_601,h_316,al_c,q_80/file.png"  ></figure><p>Nasser Bin Nawaf & Partners Holdings is proud to introduce its new logo. Simplicity and easiness of recognition were the key factors in the design of the new corporate identity. Looking to a future where NBN Holdings takes a bigger part in Qatar's economy, the new corporate branding showcases where we want to b</p>

<p>e in the international market, and easy to remember and recognize.</p>
<blockquote>“In line with the heritage of the company, we needed a brand identity that was strong, but creative in the way that made it easily recognizable.” 
<strong>Sheikh Nasser N Al Thani</strong></blockquote><h2>A family of Shades</h2>
<p>In order to enhance the strength and visibility of the logo, all Nasser Bin Nawaf & Partners Holding subsidiaries follow the same brand identity with a distinctive uniqueness: The shades.</p>

<p>The shades were developed based on the business sector and values of each entity:</p>

<p><strong>Gold of NBN Holdings: </strong>Prestige, Prosperity, Generosity.</p>
<p><strong>Red/Maroon of Elite Security Services:</strong> Health, Courage, Life.</p>
<p><strong>Blue/Turquoise of NBN Logistics:</strong> Open Spaces, Freedom, Trust.</p>
<p><strong>Orange of NBN Real Estate:</strong> Warmth, Success, Happiness.</p>
<p><strong>Green of Premium Hospitality:</strong> Environment, Nature, Health.</p>
<p><strong>Purple of NBN Technologies:</strong> Energy, Creativity, Inspiring.</p>

]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>